Okay, let's go for it!
Yes, let's go for it!
Kanomi!
Juan!
Tokko!
Haruko!
Aki!
Hiyori!
Yoshi!
Chizuru!
Shokotan!
Mizu-king!
Okay, all of you, lock on!
Let's go for it!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'll do my best!
Yay!
Please!
Oh, there it is!
Okay, okay!
I'll do my best! Dream and dance, dream and dance
I'm going to tell you out loud, look at me, look at me, look at me.
Look. That's from yesterday.
You sure it's there?
And it's behind my water, so I almost drink it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is your water.
She hasn't drunk any water.
Amazing!
Nyukkake Kutan's asmr...
I can hear it in your voice!
I won't bite.
You read the whole thing?
Yesterday's Kanamin's first one.
It's perfect. Perfect.
And I don't know how to read everything after that.
It's just that every time a person moves, there's a shadow.
That kind of thing.
I see it.
Today is...
Season of Superlatives
the stage of the feathers of spring
Jikketsu Ichiban Tokimeki Spring Seasonal Festival
Thank you for coming to
Thank you very much!
Mr. Soko and Mr. Daichi of Super Top Mick Apple and
and Kotokun of Super Top Mick
I am Shiori Yoshikawa of Super Top Mick Lin.
This is Yoshino Aichi from Green. We are ready for the day!
We were ready for a super hot day.
Can you guys speak up a lot?
Let's have fun together.
Wait for me!
Just a minute.
Still laughing over there.
Just a little bit.
He's here today.
I'm here today.
We're gonna make it today.
I don't know. I don't know. It's just a hunch.
Hanami!
Julia!
Toko!
Haruka!
Aki!
Yuri!
All of the Cho-TokiMeki Exhibition
LOCK OFF! LOVE LOVE LOVE! Please start with the number!
I'm sure you're weak! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
ahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! Go!
This is the time for the future, This is the time for the future,
Maybe it starts with protection!
Such a time,
I don't want it! 마지막으로... 일하지! 일하지! 마지막으로...
일하지! 일하지!
마지막으로...
마지막으로... 일하지! 일하지! Kampung Kampung Kampung Kampung Kampung Kampung
Kampung Kampung
Congratulations Kampung Kampung Kampung Kampung Kampung
Head,
Because I found it.
Let's go, I'm going upstairs.
Oh, and I'm in an elevator. It's an elevator, so it's comfortable.
It's hot. How is it? Are you okay? For everyone. Are you okay? Are they cute?
They said, "Hmm.
Oh, man.
Three more songs to go.
It's too soon.
I wonder when I'll see you again.
Oh, my God.
Encore, encore, encore.
I can hear them.
I can hear you just fine.I can hear you just fine.
I wonder if you'll be surprised.
I wonder if they'll call me Aki-chan.
I'm sure they will.
I don't think newcomers to the school will know that we're coming so close.
I'll try to make them think, "Wow!
I'll have fun.
Yes, that's right.
I hope they'll take pretty pictures of me.
I'm going to meet everyone.
I'm going to be cute.
He says he's feeling free.
Soon?
Soon.
What number did you get?
Here we go.
It's hot.
Three more songs.
It's easy.
me.
me... me...
meme meme meme meme meme meme meme meme
me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, my gosh!
Oh my gosh!
July!
What?
Listen, listen!
Wait, our birthdays are the next and the next day!
Oh, my God!
Wait, we're stopping!
I'll walk! Get in the car!
I'll walk!
Walk with us!
Make sure you all put it on your schedule!
Have them put it on their schedule.
Please do! Please!
Please!
Yes, I mean it,
By all means,
Please pass this on to the local people.
Thank you very much.
Please do.
Yes, that's all I have to say,
Once again, I'd like to share my thoughts on today's show.
I would like to leave the Hanami.
Please do so.
Okay, so today, everyone.
Uh, what?
Huh?
Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? 김지아, 서정아, 서정아 여리조심 아너무 너무
You can't do this! Yay! With the six of us, the promoters, and everyone's voices.
I believe that this is the best live performance!
So we will be there!
I want to come back to this big, big Saitama Super Arena
I want to come back to this big Saitama Super Irena with all of you.
It may be a very big dream
But if we all do our best to pursue our dreams together
I'm sure we can make such a big dream come true if we all do our best and keep chasing our dreams together.
I hope we can make such a big dream come true together
Let's become more powerful than ever!
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy I'm crying!
Seriously?
Wow!
You can see!
This Daruma doll...
A while ago at the time of the Corona Disaster
When I couldn't perform with everyone
We had a no-show at Saitama Super Arena.
When we came back to this venue, we said
I said, "Let's put another eye in it. I said I'd put another eye in.
I said, "Let's put another eye in," and it turned out to be the Daruma doll I promised.
I didn't think I would compose a Daruma doll while saying all this, and now I can finally put it in.
I'm so happy to finally be able to put it in, thank you. I'll put it in!
I'm so happy!
Hey, do you remember what I meant?
When Aki-chan turns 20 years old,
Saya and my daughter Panlina...
"Let's do Santa Croma" with Saya and her daughter Panrina.
"Let's have a Santa Clauma" with Saya and her daughter Panrina.
I don't care.
I was just watching that! Cover club!
He's a senior, our senior.
I'm 15, so I'm 5 years older than you.
I'm not quite a senior yet, but I'm still looking forward to working with you.
I'm still looking forward to working with you.
We are,
I would like to have my own group of members in the club,
I would like to have a solo group with a member of the club.
We would like to have a solo event with the members of the club.
We have been talking about the Saitama Super Arena for a long time, and we have said in various interviews that our next goal is the Saitama Super Arena.
Then they took us there.
Thanks to all of you, we are able to stand on the big stage like a dream, Saitama Super Arena.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Oh no!
Yes, I'll put it back then!
I'm so happy!
congratulations!
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Yay!
Congratulations!
Yeah! Yes!
Yes!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Yeah!
Now, I'm, I'm hugging you right now.
I'm holding you. I'm crying.
Here you go.
I'll try my best to be with you again.
Please.
Go to operations.
Yes, sir.
Good luck after this.
Good luck.
Yes, so Tokimeki Spring Spring Stage 2024 has ended.
Thank you very much.
It really was a spring stage.
Yes, it was.
Everyone in the wand really got the audience excited.
I heard that they changed the sound and made it more exciting. I liked it because I didn't like what I couldn't always do, but the sound was different and it was more exciting,
I'm starting to like what I can't do all the time.
And then, the tour and this year's Tokikuri were announced!
Wow!
It's going to be a great year!
I was just saying a while ago that I love this year!
I was talking about how it's not good at all, and then I was like,
I'm done! I'm done! And then it was over.
It's become a big deal.
Paprika and paprika.
Paprika and paprika and paprika.
It's all we have now.
Daruma.
This is Daruma.
Papri is also something like Daruma. Papri is also something like a daruma.
Same color.
We're going to perform at Saitama Super Arena!
Oh my gosh!
This eye is about 4 years ago?
Four or five years ago?
When I put my eyes in...
Yay!
I'm so happy!
When SSA was announced, it was the first thing I did.
Daruma! Daruma!
Daruma, right?
I kept him all this time.
I'm sorry, friend.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
We all have tours,
We will also be going overseas,
Super Leader has a lot of things coming up this year,
Let's make this year the best year ever together!
Let's make it the best year ever!
I will be waiting for you. Thank you very much. Let's make this year the best year ever together! I'll be waiting for you!
Thank you very much!
So, the two-day show is over now!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you so much for this show!
Thank you very much!
Rakuten is the best!
Thank you very much! Thank you so much! Thank you so much for the warm welcome from the fans.
That's what I was worried about the most.
So I was so relieved and we sang together.
The first time I met Pio was on the radio.
Many people told me on the radio that they liked you, Mr. Kurosawa.
I've heard from many people. I heard from many people that they really like this girl.
I was very happy to hear that, and that's why I'm so grateful to Kiyo-chan for allowing me to work with her by providing the music.
That's why I'm so grateful to Kiyo-chan for allowing me to work with her by providing the music for this project.
First of all, she's cute.
I've been a big fan of Battle of Okinawa ever since I got involved with it.
I became a big fan of Battle of Okinawa too!
I hope you will continue to love the song
I hope you will continue to love it!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. The first day
The first day, the people who were standing on the stage were really excited from the opening, weren't they?
That's right. It was completely amazing. They were really excited because of the costumes and the fact that it had been a long time since we had performed live.
After that, they kept cheering and getting really excited. After the show, they continued to get really excited about the 1,000 yen and all sorts of other things.
I have the impression that the concert was very hot.
Sweat was dripping on the floor.
I got something in my eyes.
I was sweating so much.
I'm not the type to sweat that much, but it was like a waterfall.
I think it was partly because I was wearing a long-sleeved costume.
I was really hot and sweating all the time.
It was that hot at the concert, and I could feel the enthusiasm of all the members of the promotion department,
It was such a hot show, and I felt the enthusiasm of all the members of the promotion department, so I felt again how great it was to be at a live concert.
It was great to go abroad.
You said you wanted to go abroad, but I wondered if you could go because of the stars or something like that. I had a feeling that I wanted to go abroad, but I didn't think so.
But I never thought so.
I've never been to Korea or anywhere else, not even in private,
It is private, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm also wondering what kind of audience we'll have, and of course there will be people from Japan, but I'm not sure.
Of course, there will be people from Japan, but we have had people from Korea come to our online benefit events and so on.
We have had people from Korea come to Japan for online benefit events, but this is the first time for us to go to see them.
but this is the first time for us to go and see them.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how the atmosphere will be.
April is coming to an end, right?
Tomorrow is the end of April.
So it's actually 7 months.
Isn't that fast? I'm...
I was just thinking how amazing it is. I thought it was great.
You know, people were talking about it in their impressions.
You know, there was a tour, and they were going overseas.
And then they're going overseas, and then they're going to Saitama Super Arena,
I thought, "Oh, isn't that great? I thought, "That's great.
The tour ends in September. I am really happy and thankful to the staff.
I'm really happy, and I'm thankful to the staff. I felt grateful to the staff and the publicity staff.
The two people who made the model.
Yes, that's right.
I'm from Saitama, so I'm here.
Yes, we made the model.
We had a dream to have the festival in Saitama Super Arena someday, didn't we? We wanted to do it at Saitama Super Arena because it was a big venue in our hometown.
So the day when we can stand there will come.
It is a venue that everyone dreams of.
It was also a dreamy venue.
Well, I was not so sure about it,
But now the day has been decided,
I'm just going to go for it.
Let's go for it.
We are normal,
Hitokoro came on the stage as MC,
I was quite frustrated when I was at the concert that my idol Fujii, the standard-bearer, was going to perform at.
To be honest.
And I wanted to do it again someday, you know?
This is the backstage area where we can make that happen,
I will do my best to make it a great success. It was a role where we could make that happen.
I will do my best to make it a big success. I hope you will all follow me. Please bring 100 friends.
I'll be waiting for you. Thank you very much.
Yes, it's been three months since we last talked on the phone. I thought it's been so long,
I was surprised that so much time has passed, but everyone's enthusiasm was so high,
I could feel it on the stage,
It was a really happy time.
I was really happy to see a live band playing rock music,
JUIA is wearing a very fancy hairdo this time.
What do you call it on the second day?
How do you say it?
Cold and warm. Cold and warm. I thought this would hurt, but on the second day, how do you say it? What do you say? Sweet drunkenness.
I thought this was going to hurt, but it doesn't hurt at all.I thought this would hurt, but it doesn't hurt at all.
To the Rock.
Went to the Rock, GT shipped.
I've been wondering when it was going to be.
All at once they announced November.
I guess 789, the tour is at 789
But first lyrics 7 and so on.
And Ibaraki.
My first time...
There are a lot of lyrics that are new to me.
I'm looking forward to Korean.
And there are two overseas concerts
A one-man show in Korea...
I've never been to Korea.
I've never been to Korea, so I'm really looking forward to it.
And all the MC's will be in Korean.
Oh, what am I going to do?
I'm going to introduce myself and my favorite songs are in Korean.
Oh, I'll certainly try my best to play along!
Yes, I'm looking forward to it!
I'm so excited about Korean!
If there's an overseas stop on the tour, does that mean we'll be going overseas?
So it's almost a little bit of an overseas tour?
Yes, so I guess you can call it an Asian tour.
It's not really an Asian tour.
A little bit Asia tour
I'll do my best!
Oh my God! I cry every time I go. When we had Junior in 2012, I honestly thought that I wouldn't be able to put it in my eyes,
But now, after four years, the time has finally come for me to be able to enter,
I had also set "Seiyo Seiyo" as the next big goal for Yokowari,
I thought I would be super happy if I could do it within a couple of years,
I couldn't believe that they wanted Junior,
I couldn't believe that I wanted a junior.
I was like, "What? I'm super happy.
It's too soon, too soon.
I'm not good enough as I am now, so I'm going to work harder and do my best so that I can accumulate more and become more courageous.
I will do my best.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Really, when we had that no-show and the bicycles came and had a field day,
The design was really that good, just think of the super pace going in there,
It's going to be bad again.
It's bad.
But the next time it starts, it won't be anything.
Because I'm going to be 20 years old.
I mean, you turn 20 and your first role is gone.
A little bit flabby.
So, a more evolved Mr. Sugata and I will actually do our best.
Come to the two of us.
Please open your schedule.
It's 28, all of us.
It's Christmas.
I love Christmas.
I'm happy, I'm happy.
See you soon.
I'll do my best.
Good work. Good work. The music danced with the gorgeousness of Kizun Band's performance.
The music was dancing. It looked good without being overpowering, and the good parts of the songs were alive,
It was great.
It felt great.
When you sing and the rhythm matches with the song, it feels great,
And the shouting was really fun, too.
It was a really great performance.
Thank you so much to everyone in 2017.
The stage was long and sideways, which made it interesting.
Everyone said it was easy to see.
It was easy for us to see everyone's faces, too.
So it was great.
Then came the surprise announcement,
Mr. Korezawa came to this concert.
I'm really happy.
Because, you know, there is someone I've always liked,
Since when do you like him?
Quite a bit, because maybe when I had my birthday party at Arikankaku, I think it's pretty good, because maybe when we had a birthday party with an audience,
When we had a birthday party with an audience, the song for the audience?
Very front.
Two weeks ago, Kurosawa-san performed a song called "Laughing Maiden" in front of everyone.
Laughing Maiden.
That's it.
But before that, I would say I was in junior high school.
Really.
Oh, really?
That's right.
We wrote a song together,
I want to be on stage with you.
And we sing together a lot, don't we?
Really?
A dreamy position for a singer.
Singer position?
Not a singer's position.
I wish I could have sung with you.
Thank you very much. Yes. I want to be in the singing position. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
When the dream changes, until a different dream happens,
After all, some of you are captivated by Ms. Furusawa,
I was, too.
I think there are a lot of you out there.
I want to go to the concert.
I want to go.
I wonder how many times they want to go on tour this year,
Maybe, you know, even if it's not overseas or something.
That's what he really said.
Oh, now you hit it.
I've always wanted to come to Korea.
I've always wanted to come to Korea, you know, just to see the sights.
But I think I'm probably a little free in the day.
I mean, I've been in Korea for...
Two years in Korea? Two years in Korea?
Yeah, two years.Yeah, two years.
So you're going back to Japan?
I was in Japan half of July and Indonesia about 3 days in August.
27 degrees or less?
So you're going back to Japan?
We're both going overseas, overseas, overseas.
But we have to buy a big suitcase.
Aah! No!
I'm getting excited!
But you know, I really hear that Indonesian people from Korea are coming to our benefit events these days,
So, by all means, let's all of you in Japan go together.
Let's go together.
So, how far are we going to go with the one-ban live?
One band live? Not a festival, but a one-band show?
What about a one-band show?
It's a little loud. Are you okay with that? Now. And then... and then... oh!
It's bad, isn't it?
It's a bad birthday, isn't it?
It's so early for a flower, but it's already so early,
When I said, "Welcome back," people would write in interviews, "What is your next goal?
I was asked in an interview, "When will it be next year?
Next year, sarang will be at the venue.
The moment you see "sa," the venue will already be in bloom.
What if it's not?
It's already sa, and it will be sa.
I know, sardine.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I wonder if it's really great.
You know, I've been to Saitama Super Arena twice, right?
Yeah.
Um..,
First, the light in Thailand.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I just formed the band.
I think if you did YouTube or something like that.
I remember when we were trying really hard, and when we played a no-show.
That's where I remember it.I'm pretty sure that's where I remember it.
Do you remember that? Didn't you feel like that was the point of the pinlight?
It was amazing. But really, we didn't have that many pans at that time,
But they came,
Maybe it was because we had a lot of love from Piton's sisters and other pan people,
But it was really beautiful.
It was really beautiful. Saitama is amazing. This is the reason why our seniors started to hang idols on TV at work,
I thought at that time that if I saw this view, I could do my best no matter what,
If I can see that view, I'm not forced to do anything.
There is no time.
Only one or two months.
This was a little over a year, so it's amazing.
It took a little over a year for Makuhari, too, and it was shorter than that,
The capacity has increased, but it's still short.
It's a little shorter.
It's amazing.
This is nothing.
It's a challenge, really.
We have a lot to reflect on in today's show,
We'll make sure to perfect those areas as well.
I heard it's hard to control the venue.
Yes! You did a great job, Loose.
Thank you so much, staff.
I wonder how long they've been holding it back.
Just thinking about it. Yes. Thank you, thank you, thank you, Mr. Staff. You've been holding it down from the very beginning. Just thinking about that.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you thank you thank you.
For the next 8 months, we will work hard and run through the tour so that we can become the idol that fits within Saitama Super,
We will make a lot of people fall in love with us and do our best in SSA!
Will you give me a big kiss at SSA?
Next time, I'll hit on you.
Yesterday, my beauty gave me a kiss.
One second after she kissed me, I knew I was going to do it tomorrow.
I'm going to give you an extra big kiss at SSA today.
You might see me there, so please come.
Thank you very much.
This is me.
nini
meniniWhen I laugh, it sure seems like the world is shining.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy
Because if I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
And somewhere I'll get my body wet again
I wonder if it's not cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart
I can tell you now the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
So that I can smile even when it rains
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shining
It's as if my heart is in a sunny mood
Rainbow pools of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me, the streets sparkle after the rain
Thank you for watching I'm going to wear a rainbow dress.